JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 13
WE PICKED UP SOMETHING CRAZY!
BRIGHT DEER
LONG DISTANCE BUS
TO SAPPORO
JOSUKE HIGASHIKATA
SUPER ABSORBENT
ADULT DIAPERS
HERMIT PURPLE
EPISODE 14
LET'S GO TO
THE MANGA ARTIST'S HOUSE, PART 1